<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project Comparison on IceFireDB Documentation</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/project-comparison/</link><description>Recent content in Project Comparison on IceFireDB Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/project-comparison/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OrbitDB</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/project-comparison/orbitdb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/project-comparison/orbitdb/</guid><description>Compared with OrbitDB # OrbitDB is a serverless, distributed, peer-to-peer database.
OrbitDB uses IPFS as its data storage and IPFS Pubsub and uses CRDTs to automatically sync databases with peers, achieving strong eventual consistency - when all updates are eventually received, all nodes will have the same state.
IceFireDB is a database built for web3 and web2,The core mission of the project is to help applications quickly achieve decentralization,built for Data dao.</description></item><item><title>ThreadDB</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/project-comparison/threaddb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/project-comparison/threaddb/</guid><description>Compared with ThreadDB # ThreadDB is a serverless, distributed, peer-to-peer database.
IceFireDB is a database built for web3 and web2,The core mission of the project is to help applications quickly achieve decentralization,built for Data dao.
Database ThreadDB IceFireDB system target P2P Databases A decentralized database platform built for Data dao. storage engine support IPFS goleveldb、badger、IPFS、CRDT、IPFS-LOG、OSS network support type P2P P2P、RAFT、NATS Data type support SQL KV、Strings、Hashes、Lists、Sorted Sets、Sets、SQL、PubSub Software integration method Binary software integration Software library integration, binary software integration、web3 platform integration web3 support No smart contract plan Smart contracts are being supported、Build data dao database platform computer language used to implement Go Go Ecological client language Go Any client that supports the redis、mysql protocol Thanks ThreadDB # Thanks to ThreadDB for letting us see the excellent implementation of decentralized SQL database.</description></item></channel></rss>