<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Designs on IceFireDB Documentation</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/</link><description>Recent content in Designs on IceFireDB Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OverView</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/overview/</guid><description> OverView #</description></item><item><title>Network layer</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/network/</guid><description>Network layer design # The network layer undertakes the work of inter-node networking, inter-node data distribution, and inter-node data consistency consensus. The network layer of IceFireDB is divided into two layers according to the distance of the physical network link:
Data consistency network layer for short-distance networks. Decentralized database network layer for wide-distance network. The above two different network layers are supported by different technologies and have different requirements for data consistency sensitivity and timeliness.</description></item><item><title>Storage layer</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/storage/</guid><description>Storage layer design # The storage layer is responsible for data storage, and the data storage here includes different storage media of web2 and web3. For web2, the storage media we face includes disk, OSS, and for web3, the storage media we face includes IPFS, blockchain, and smart contracts.Currently, the storage types supported by IceFireDB mainly include the following.
Engine type describe Driver directory LevelDB LevelDB is a fast key-value storage library written at Google that provides an ordered mapping from string keys to string values.</description></item><item><title>Protocol layer</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/protocol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/protocol/</guid><description>Protocol layer design # A good access method of the application can accelerate the growth of the application ecology, and a good protocol design can reduce the transformation cost of the stock application, so the protocol layer is an important component of the IceFireDB software stack. The communication protocol of IceFireDB-NoSQL fully integrates the Redis RESP protocol, which mainly includes the following two parts of the protocol:
Data control protocol: Complete support for RESP clients, supporting functional requirements for database data access.</description></item><item><title>Codec layer</title><link>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/codec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.icefiredb.xyz/icefiredb_docs/icefiredb/icefiredb-nosql/designs/codec/</guid><description>Codec layer design # The codec layer is the glue of the IceFireDB data expression layer, because the bottom layer of IceFireDB supports many storage engines, including centralized storage such as web2 disk, OSS, leveldb, and badger, as well as web3&amp;rsquo;s IPFS, crdt-kv, and IPFS-LOG For this kind of decentralized storage, the storage interface provided by any kind of storage is simple and not standardized. The codec layer of IceFireDB-NoSQL is abstracted through a unified driver layer, and by encoding and decoding many instruction semantics into a KV model, a richer data expression layer is built to support more data scenarios, such as Strings\Hashs\Sets\Lists \Sorted Sets.</description></item></channel></rss>